# **ORIT LESHEM**

755 Dunboyne Cres' | London, ON | N5X 1X9 | 519-933-0408 | azmono@gmail.com Portfolio: Orit Leshem

#### **Profile**

A self-motivated, goal-oriented full-stack developer specializing in JavaScript, Node.js and React.js.

I have an MBA as well as a Software Engineering Immersive certification and Coding Academy Israel full-stack developer diploma; I am bilingual in English and Hebrew

## **Core Skills/Competencies**

- JavaScript
- Html
- CSS
- React.js
- Node.js
- Angular

- Vue.js
- Python
- Django
- Mongoose
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL

- ASW S3
- jQuery
- GitHub
- Management
- Problem-Solving
- Flexibility and Innovation

## **Relevant Work Experience**

### **Full-Stack Developer Fellow**

Coding Academy, Tel-Aviv, Israel

November 2022 – February 2023

- Used React.js, Vue.js, Angular Node.js and MongoDB to develop full-stack applications
- Collaborated with team members to develop applications from planning to execution
- Demonstrated efficient performance while inspiring team members to meet expectations

# **Software Engineering Fellow**

April 2021 – June 2021

General Assembly, Toronto, Canada

- Used React.js, Node.js, MongoDB, Phyton and SQL to develop full-stack applications
- Worked with the team on all aspects of application development, from start to finish
- Performed efficiently and motivated team members to achieve team goals

### **Work Experience**

### **Front Desk Supervisor**

September 2021 – September 2022

Idlewyld Inn & Spa, London, Canada

- Demonstrated exceptional customer service skills by effectively managing and resolving quest complaints, increasing customer satisfaction ratings.
- Implemented effective communication, resulting in improved customer service delivery.
- Utilized strong sales skills to upsell hotel services and amenities successfully

# **ORIT LESHEM**

755 Dunboyne Cres' | London, ON | N5X 1X9 | 519-933-0408 | azmono@gmail.com Portfolio: Orit Leshem

## **General Manager**

January 2018 - January 2021

Kinneret-mall shopping center, Jordan Valley, Israel

- Created and executed sales strategy raising appraisal value by 14.7% over two years
- Transformed inner layout by 10% to accommodate two new Mega-retail stores
- Managed 40 properties to provide a first-class rate shopping experience
- Collaborated with the local municipality to provide catering solutions for 500 employees

## Business consultant / Business development manager Freelance, Tel-Aviv, Israel

Magen David Adom (Israeli Red Cross first aid organization)

January 2014 – January 2018

- Co-Founded an Israeli Cyber services company, launched within 3 months of Founding
- Established and managed a Sales and services call center for Afikim Electric vehicles
- Built and trained sales and support teams and set up the IT service infrastructure
- Consulted on HR management and sales training programs for small and medium privately held businesses

#### Education

Education	
Coding Academy Israel, Full Stack Developer	2023
Coding Academy Israel, Canada, remote	
SEI Software Engineering Immersive, Full Stack Developer	2021
General Assembly, Toronto, Canada	2021
MBA Marketing and advertising specialization	2007
The college for management, Rishon-Lezion, Israel	2007
Bachelor of Business Marketing and HR specialization	2004
The college for management, Rishon-Lezion, Israel	
Awards	
Awarded the International Advertising Association's Diploma in Marketing	
Communications	
The college for management, Rishon-Lezion, Israel	2007
Bachelor of business Graduated with honour – Magna cum Laude	
The college for management, Rishon-Lezion, Israel	2004
Volunteer experience	
*Oldificor experience	
Emergency Medical Responder (EMR) and Ambulance driver	2016 – 2021